Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 4. Smith Administration Records, 1977-1992
    - Department of Educational Opportunity, 1978-1984 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Department of Educational Psychology, 1982-1989 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Department of English, 1985-1989 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Department of Exceptional Education, 1983-1988 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Department of Film, 1982-1987 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Department of Financial Aid, 1985-1987 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Department of French and Italian, 1977-1986 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Department of Geography, 1985-1988 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Department of Geological and Geophysical Sciences, 1980-1985 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Department of German, 1978-1987 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Department of Health Sciences, 1982-1988 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Department of Hebrew Studies, 1984-1988 (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Department of History, 1985-1989 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Department of Human Kinetics, 1981-1989 (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - Department of Learning Skills and Educational Opportunity, 1973-1989 (Box 116, Folder 31)
    - Department of Linguistics, 1979-1986 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - Department of Mass Communication, 1985-1989 (Box 116, Folder 33)
    - Department of Mathematical Sciences, 1980-1988 (Box 116, Folder 34)
    - Department of Mechanical Engineering, 1983-1988 (Box 116, Folder 35)
    - Department of Military Science, 1982-1986 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Department of Music, 1985-1989 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Department of Natural Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Department of Personnel Services, 1986-1989 (Box 117, Folder 4-8)
    - Department of Philosophy, 1979-1987 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Department of Physics, 1984-1988 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Department of Planning and Construction, 1981-1988 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Department of Political Science, 1983-1989 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Department of Psychology, 1981-1989 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Department of Slavic Languages, 1981-1986 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Department of Sociology, 1982-1987 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1985-1989 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Department of Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1982-1987 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Department of Student Health, 1980-1985 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Department of Theatre and Dance, 1982-1987 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Department of Urban Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Disabled Students, 1985-1988 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Distinguished Professorships, 1984-1987 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Division of Administrative Affairs, 1984-1987 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Division of Arts and Humanities, Executive Committee, 1980-1989 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Division of Outreach and Continuing Education, 1985-1989 (Box 117, Folder 25-26)
    - Division of the Professions, Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - Divisional Committees, 1973-1986 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - Doctor of Engineering Program Conversion, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - Downer Buildings, 1982-1983 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Drop Policies, 1987-1988 (Box 117, Folder 31)
    - Early Childhood Exceptional Education Program, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Economic Benefits Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Editorial Board Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Educational Communications Division, 1978-1989 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - EDUCOM, 1975-1989 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Elderhostel, 1982-1988 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Emeritus Status, 1978-1987 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Employee Assistance Program, 1988-1989 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Employment and Training Institute, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Employment Contracts, 1977-1984 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Employment Relations Office, 1987-1989 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Energy Conservation, 1982-1983 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Engelmann Hall, 1974-1984 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - English and a Second Language Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Enrollment, Graduate Students, 1984-1989 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Enrollment Projections, 1982-1986 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1985-1989 (Box 118, Folder 18-22)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1987-1988 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Equal Opportunity Office, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Estate of Gerow W. Turner, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Ethics Board Code, 1984-1988 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Ethnic Studies, 1979-1987 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Evaluation of Administration, 1979-1987 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Executive Salary Plan, 1983-1987 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Extension Policy Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - Facilities, Use of, 1977-1988 (Box 118, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Development, 1984-1989 (Box 118, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Governance, 1980-1981 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Merit Appeals Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Faculty, New, 1984-1988 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Recognition Fund, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Resignations, 1988-1989 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Rights and Responsibilities Committee, 1973-1985 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1984-1986 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Salary Committee, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Senate, 1978-1988 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Senate Budget Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Workload, 1986-1988 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1985-1986 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Farewell Reception, Clifford V. Smith, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Federal Aid to Institutions, 1974-1983 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Fee Schedule and Policies, 1981-1987 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Field Stations, 1979-1989 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Financial Aid, 1988-1989 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Financial Emergencies, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Financial Services, 1980-1988 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - First Bank Milwaukee, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - First Friday, 1982-1989 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - First Wisconsin, 1977-1986 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Five Year Reviews, 1983-1988 (Box 119, Folder 22-23)
    - Fixed Term Academic Staff Appointments, 1974-1984 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Fleet, 1974-1984 (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Florentine Opera Board, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Ford Foundation, 1976-1989 (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Language and Literature, 1981-1988 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Foundations, 1986-1989 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Freshman Class, 1981-1987 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Fromkin Memorial Lecture, 1984-1987 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Fulbright Scholars, 1987-1989 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Fund Raising, 1986-1987 (Box 119, Folder 33-34)
    - Funding Reductions, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - Gamaliel Chair, 1981-1982 (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - Garland/Pearse Halls, 1982-1986 (Box 119, Folder 37)
    - Gateway to Engineering, Science and Technology Program (GEST), 1989 (Box 119, Folder 38)
    - Gay Community, 1973-1982. (Box 119, Folder 39)
    - Gender Equity Task Force, 1984-1986 (Box 119, Folder 40)
    - General Education Requirements (GER), 1984-1986 (Box 119, Folder 41)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1986-1990 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Golda Meir Library, 1985-1989 (Box 120, Folder 2-3)
    - Golda Meir Library, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Golda Meir Library, Stage III Building Project, 1976-1984 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Governor's VTAE Study Commission, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, 1986-1989 (Box 120, Folder 6-8)
    - Graduate Retention, 1982-1986 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Graduate School, 1985-1989 (Box 120, Folder 10-18)
    - Graduate School, Extramural Funding, 1987-1988 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Graduate School Fellowship Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Graduate School Research Awards, 1985-1989 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School Research Committee, 1980-1988 (Box 121, Folder 4-5)
    - Graduate School, Research Incentive Program, 1986-1987 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Graduate School Student Enrollment and Recruitment, 1982-1988 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Student Staff, 1985-1988 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Grand Viennese Ball, 1982-1987 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Great Lakes Research Facility, 1976-1988 (Box 121, Folder 10-11)
    - Greater Milwaukee Committee for Community Development, 1985-1986 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Halyard Scholarships, 1981-1983 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Hartford Avenue, 1974-1982 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Hazardous Waste, 1986-1988 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Hearing and Appeals Committee, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - High School Equivalency Program, 1984-1986 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Higher Education Aids Board, 1983 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Hispanic Students, 1989-1991 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Holds, 1978-1984 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Homecoming, 1982-1986 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Honorary Degree Candidates for Commencement, 1987-1989 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 121, Folder 23-27)
    - Honorary Societies, 1978-1986 (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Honors Program, 1980-1989 (Box 121, Folder 29-30)
    - Human Rights Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Human Subjects Review Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - IBM, 1980-1989 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Impact Statement on UWM's Influence on the Milwaukee Metropolitan Community, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Inauguration, Clifford V. Smith, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Inauguration, Clifford V. Smith, 1986, VHS videotape (Box 141)
    - Indefinite Status, 1986-1989 (Box 122, Folder 5-6)
    - Indirect Costs, 1975-1988 (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
    - Industry-University Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Information Systems, 1987-1989 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - In-Person Registration, 1986-1987 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Institute of World Affairs, 1983-1989 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Institutional Safety and Hazards Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Interinstitutional Agreements, General, 1982-1985 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Interinstitutional Agreements, UWM/UWEX, 1976-1985 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - International Activities/Education, 1983-1988 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - International Agreements, 1980-1986 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - International Business Studies Center, 1986-1987 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - International Relations Major, 1973-1989 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - International Studies and Programs, 1985-1988 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - International Studies and Programs, Faculty Advisory Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - International Task Force, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - International Teaching Assistants, 1987-1988 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Interpreter Training Program, 1986-1987 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Inventory Report, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Israel, 1985-1989 (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Japan, 1984-1986 (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Jobs, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1979-1989 (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Journal Communications, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Keulks, George W., 1984-1989 (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - Klotsche Center, 1980-1989 (Box 122, Folder 32)
    - Labor Leaders, 1981-1983 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Laboratory for Surface Studies, 1985-1987 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Language Resource Center, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Lapham Hall Science Center, 1985-1987 (Box 123, Folder 4-7)
    - Law Studies, 1982-1984 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Layton Foundation Endowment, 1983-1988 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Leases, 1974-1980 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Lectures Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Binder, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Briefings, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Fiscal Bureau, 1976-1987 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Legislative Receptions, 1985-1986 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Legislators' Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 123, Folder 16-17)
    - Lobbying, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Long Range Capital Development Plan, 1989-1995, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Marquette University, 1972-1987 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Masters in Industrial and Labor Relations Degree Program, 1980-1987 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Medical College of Wisconsin, 1977-1989 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Medical Records Administration Program, 1978-1985 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Medical Technology Program, 1984-1987 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Merger, 1976-1978 (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Metropolitan Milwaukee Association of Commerce, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Metropolitan Milwaukee Civic Alliance, 19814982 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Midwest Universities Energy Consortium, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - Midwestern Universities Alliance, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - Milwaukee Area Technical College, 1986-1989 (Box 123, Folder 30)
    - Milwaukee Area Technical College/UWM Coordinating Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 123, Folder 31)
    - Milwaukee, City of, 1985-1989 (Box 123, Folder 32)
    - Milwaukee, City of, Office of the Mayor, 1970-1989 (Box 123, Folder 33)
    - Milwaukee Community Journal, 1988-1989 (Box 123, Folder 34)
    - Milwaukee County, 1976-1989 (Box 123, Folder 35)
    - Milwaukee County Research Park, 1986-1988 (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - Milwaukee Foundation, 1983-1987 (Box 123, Folder 37-38)
    - Milwaukee Foundation, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee Initiative, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee International Health Training Center, 1986-1987 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Milwaukee Jazz Experience, 1986-1987 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Milwaukee Journal, 1982-1987 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Milwaukee Labor Force Coordinating Council, 1982 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Milwaukee Public Library, 1973-1982 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Milwaukee Public Museum, 1978-1982 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1984-1989 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools
      - UWM Coordinating Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 124, Folder 10-12)
      - UWM Joint Projects, 1984-1989 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Milwaukee Regional Medical Center, 1977-1989 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Milwaukee School of Engineering, 1977-1986 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Milwaukee Sentinel, 1984-1987 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Minority Academic Achievement Scholarship Program, 1984-1989 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Minority Affairs Council, 1988-1989 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Minority/Disadvantaged Advisory Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Minority/Disadvantaged Coordinator, 1984-1989 (Box 124, Folder 20-23)
    - Minority/Disadvantaged Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 124, Folder 24)
    - Minority/Disadvantaged Student Programs Advisory Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Minority Faculty, 1982-1987 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Minority Information Center, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Minority Information, Non-Student, 1982-1984 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Minority Student Employment Program Proposal, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Mission Statement, 1973-1988 (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Monthly Regents' Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Names of Buildings Subcommittee, 1983-1987 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Exposition Managers, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1982-1988 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1986-1988 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, Division of Urban Affairs, 1986-1989 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1984-1989 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1985 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - National Merit Scholarship Program, 1984-1985 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - National Science Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Network Library System (NLS), 1985-1986 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Non-Academic Program Review, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Non-Represented Classified Staff, 1977-1986 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Non-Represented Classified Staff Exceptional Performance Awards, 1982-1989 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Non-Resident Tuition Remissions, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - North Central Association, 1985-1987 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Report, November 1984 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life, 1982-1985 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Occupational Therapy Program, 1979-1986 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Off-Campus Credit Courses, 1980-1985 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Off-Campus Housing Referral Service, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Off-Campus Program, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Office of Affirmative Action and Equal Opportunity, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Office of Black Student Advising, 1983-1988 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Office of Industrial Research and Technology Transfer, 1985-1989 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1987-1988 (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Office of Institutional Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Office of International Studies and Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Office of International Studies and Programs, Summary Report, 1981-1987 (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Office of the Registrar, 1985-1989 (Box 125, Folder 31-33)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Charts, 1982-1989 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Outdoor Recreational Space Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Outside Activities, 1973-1985 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Parental Involvement Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Parking and Transit Advisory Sub-committee of the Physical Environment Committee, 1983-1987 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Parking and Transit Office, 1981-1989 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Peace Studies Network, 1983-1987 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Percent for Art Program, 1985-1988 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Personnel File Policy, 1973-1984 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Services Review Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1977-1987 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Physical Education, Athletics, and Recreation, 1977-1988 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Physical Environment Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Physical Plant Services, 1981-1989 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Plaza Building Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1980-1986 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Polish-American Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Polish Studies Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Pre-College Center, 1982-1989 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Preview, 1982 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Professional Dimensions, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Professional Theatre Training Program, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Programmatic Needs, 1981-1984 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Promotions, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Property and Inventory Control Management, 1975-1984 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Proposed Mission Statement, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - Psychology Accreditation, 1980-1984 (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Public Administration Program, 1979-1987 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Public Records, 1982-1984 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Purin Hall, 1965-1983 (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - Race and Ethnicity, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Racism, 1988-1989 (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - Recruitment, 1977-1985 (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - Recruitment and Retention of Minority Students, 1986-1987 (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - Regents Study Group on the Future of the UW System, 1986-1988 (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - Rehabilitation Counseling, 1980-1985 (Box 126, Folder 37)
    - Remedial Education, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 38)
    - Remedial Instruction, 1987-1989 (Box 126, Folder 39)
    - Remodeling Projects, 1974-1983 (Box 126, Folder 40)
    - Research, 1988-1989 (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
    - Research Incentive Program, 1988 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Research Plan, 1986-1989 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Research Policy Committee, 1975-1988 (Box 127, Folder 5-6)
    - Research Profile, 1986-1988 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Retention Task Force, 1987-1989 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Retired Faculty Association, 1971-1989 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Retirement, 1985-1989 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Rexnord, 1980-1985 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Riverside University High School, 1985-1987 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - ROTC, 1985-1987 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - ROTC Officer Education Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Sabbatical Leave Program, 1985-1989 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Salary Adjustment Guidelines, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Sandburg Commons Activities Board, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Sandburg Residence Halls, 1985-1989 (Box 127, Folder 18-19)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, 1985-1989 (Box 127, Folder 20-21)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1986-1989 (Box 127, Folder 22-26)
    - School of Business Administration, 1986-1989 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
    - School of Business Administration
      - Advisory Council, 1978-1989 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Fee Increase, 1989 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Helfaer Professorship, 1973-1983 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - School of Education, 1985-1989 (Box 128, Folder 7-9)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1986-1989 (Box 128, Folder 10-12)
    - School of Library and Information Science, 1982-1989 (Box 128, Folder 13-14)
    - School of Nursing, 1986-1989 (Box 128, Folder 15-16)
    - School of Nursing
      - Accreditation, 1977-1985 (Box 128, Folder 17)
      - Master of Science Degree Program, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 18)
      - PhD Program, 1984-1986 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - School of Social Welfare, 1985-1989 (Box 128, Folder 20-21)
    - School of Urban Journalism Plan, 1984-1987 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Scott, David C, Foundation, Inc., 1982-1986 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Sea Grant Institute, 1978-1982 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Search and Screen Committee for Assistant to the Chancellor for Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Search and Screen Committee for Assistant Chancellor for University Relations, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Search and Screen Committee for the Assistant Chancellor for Student Affairs, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Search and Screen Committee for the Director of Auxiliary Services, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Search and Screen Committee for Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Secretary of the University, 1985-1987 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Segregated Fee Status Review, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Segregated Fees, 1980-1987 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Senate of the Academic Staff, 1988-1989 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Senior Honors Convocation, 1983-1989 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1983-1988 (Box 129, Folder 12-13)
    - Shaw Scholars Program, 1982-1987 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Shorewood, Village of, 1979-1986 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Signature Authorizations, 1975-1987 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Smithsonian National Associate Program, 1981-1983 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Smoking, 1966-1984 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Social Science Research Facility, 1973-1980 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Sophomore Honors Convocation, 1983-1988 (Box 129, Folder 20)